Guide to the Argus Archives Records
Argus Archives Records
- The Animals' Agenda, 1979-2002; 1979 2002; 50 linear feet
  - Animal League of Long Island (ALLI): AA1 - Bulletins, 1990s (Box 2.011, Folder 11)
  - Animal Legal Defense Fund (ALDF): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.011, Folder 12)
  - Animal Legal Defense Fund (ALDF): AA2 - Bulletins, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.011, Folder 13)
  - Animal Legal Defense Fund (ALDF): AA3 - Press releases, 1994-1998 (Box 2.011, Folder 14)
  - Animal Legal Defense Fund (ALDF): AA4 - News clippings, 1985 November 13, 1990 April 28 (Box 2.011, Folder 15)
  - Animal Legal Defense Fund (ALDF): AA5 - Annual report, 1991 (Box 2.011, Folder 16)
  - Animal Legal Defense Fund (ALDF): AA6 - Report "Animal Welfare Enforcement,", 1993 (Box 2.011, Folder 17)
  - Animal Legal Defense Fund (ALDF): AA7 - Journals Pace Environmental Law Review Vol. 3 and Vol. 4, 1986 (Box 2.011, Folder 18)
  - Animal Legal Defense Fund (ALDF): AA8 - Legal Opinion, 1997 December 9 (Box 2.011, Folder 19)
  - Animal Legal Defense Fund (ALDF): AA9 - Correspondence, 1985 November 1 (Box 2.011, Folder 20)
  - Animal Legislation NYC: Newsletter, 1981 Fall (Box 2.011, Folder 21)
  - Animal Legislative Action Network, Los Angeles CA.(ALAN): AA1 - Bulletin, 1995 May 8 (Box 2.011, Folder 22)
  - Animal Liberation, Baltimore MD.: AA1 - News clipping, 1982 October 7 (Box 2.011, Folder 23)
  - Animal Liberation, Baltimore MD.: AA2 - Press release, 1993 June 1 (Box 2.011, Folder 24)
  - Animal Liberation, Australia: AA1 - Calendar, 1999 (Box 2.011, Folder 25)
  - Animal Liberation, Australia: AA2 - Magazine ani - mate, 1998 Spring (Box 2.011, Folder 26)
  - Animal Liberation of Texas (ALT): AA1 - Newsletters, 1998-1999 (Box 2.011, Folder 26)
  - Animal Liberation Front Supporters Group - UK (ALFSG): AA1 - Publication, 1991 (Box 2.011, Folder 27)
  - Animal Liberation Front Supporters Group - UK (ALFSG): AA2 - News clippings, 1995 May 7 (Box 2.011, Folder 28)
  - Animal Liberation Front Supporters Group - S. Africa (ALFSG): AA1 - Press release, 1996 May 13 (Box 2.012, Folder 1)
  - Animal Liberation Action (ALA): AA1 - Essays, 1993 (Box 2.012, Folder 2)
  - Animal Liberation, Victoria: AA1 - Printed matter, 1994, 1998 (Box 2.012, Folder 3)
  - Animal Liberation, Victoria: AA2 - Postcards, 1990s (Box 2.012, Folder 4)
  - Animal Liberation, Victoria: AA3 - News clippings, 1997 February 19 (Box 2.012, Folder 5)
  - Animal Liberation, Victoria: AA4 - Published article, 1997 April 17 (Box 2.012, Folder 6)
  - Animal Liberation, Victoria: AA5 - Legal documents, 1997 February 18 (Box 2.012, Folder 7)
  - Animal Liberation League, Apple Valley MN.(ALL): AA1 - leaflets, 1997-1999 (Box 2.012, Folder 8)
  - Animal Liberation League, Apple Valley MN.(ALL): AA2 - Publication, 1970s (Box 2.012, Folder 9)
  - Animals' Liberation Movement: AA1- Bulletin, 1970s (Box 2.012, Folder 10)
  - Animal Liberation News: AA1 - Newsletters, 1974 Summer and Fall (Box 2.012, Folder 11)
  - Animal Liberation News: AA2 - Bibliography relating to vegetarianism, 1970s (Box 2.012, Folder 12)
  - Animal Liberation Network, Hunt Valley MD. (ALN): AA1 - Bulletin, 1988 (Box 2.012, Folder 13)
  - Animal Liberation Through Education and Reform (ALTER): AA1- Bulletins, 1994-1995 (Box 2.012, Folder 14)
  - Animal Lifeline of Iowa: AA1 - Newsletters, 1992-1993 (Box 2.012, Folder 15)
  - Animal Lifeline of Iowa: AA2 - News clippings, 1992 July 8 and July 16 (Box 2.012, Folder 16)
  - Animal Link: AA1 - Bulletin, 1998 (Box 2.012, Folder 17)
  - The Animal Lobby: AA1 - Newsletter, 1994 Summer (Box 2.012, Folder 18)
  - The Animal Lobby: AA2 - Bulletins, 1992, 1995 (Box 2.012, Folder 19)
  - The Animal Lovers Journal(ALJ): AA1 - Press release, 1995 (Box 2.012, Folder 20)
  - Animal Lovers Unlimited, Inc.(ALU): AA1 - Newsletter, 1987 October (Box 2.012, Folder 21)
  - Animal Lovers Volunteer Association (ALVA): AA1 - Bulletins, 1991 (Box 2.012, Folder 22)
  - The Animal Medical Center N.Y.N.Y.(AMC): AA1 - Newsletter, 1998 Spring (Box 2.012, Folder 23)
  - Animal Nation, West River MD.: AA1 - Press releases, 1996 (Box 2.012, Folder 24)
  - Animal Nation, West River MD.: AA2 - Media kit, 1996 (Box 2.012, Folder 25)
  - Animal Orphanage, Denver Co.: AA1 - Pamphlets, 1987 (Box 2.012, Folder 26)
  - The Animal Orphanage, Voorhees NJ.: AA1 - Bulletins, 1996 (Box 2.012, Folder 27)
  - Animal Outreach of The Mother Load: AA1 - Newsletter, 1995 March (Box 2.012, Folder 28)
  - Animal Passion: AA1 - Newsletter, 1997 Spring (Box 2.012, Folder 29)
  - Animal Peace, New Orleans LA.: AA1 - Report on the U.S. Army Ballistic Wound Research Conducted at Louisiana State University, 1998, 1989 (Box 2.012, Folder 30)
  - Animal People, Clinton WA.: AA1 - Bulletin, 1994 May 30 (Box 2.012, Folder 31)
  - Animal People, Clinton WA.: AA2 - Published articles, 1993, 1996 (Box 2.012, Folder 32)
  - Animal People, Clinton WA.: AA3 - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2.012, Folder 32)
  - Animal Place: AA1 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.012, Folder 33)
  - Animal Place: AA2 - Comic books, 1990s (Box 2.012, Folder 34)
  - Animal Place: AA3 - Cook book, 1998 (Box 2.012, Folder 35)
  - Animal Place: AA4 - Grant proposal, 1997 (Box 2.012, Folder 36)
  - Animal Political Action Committee (ANPAC): AA1 - Bulletin, circa 1986 (Box 2.012, Folder 37)
  - Animal Political Action Committee (ANPAC): AA2 - Voters guide, 1985 (Box 2.012, Folder 38)
  - The Animal Project (TAP): AA1 - Bulletins, 1980s (Box 2.012, Folder 39)
  - Animal Protection Association, Bartlett NJ (APA): AA1 - Newsletters, 1994-1998 (Box 2.012, Folder 40)
  - Animal Protection Association, Bartlett NJ (APA): AA2 - Correspondence, 1998 May 6 (Box 2.012, Folder 41)
  - Animal Protection of New Mexico: AA1 - Press releases, 1998 (Box 2.013, Folder 1)
  - Animal Protection of New Mexico: AA2 - Pamphlets, 1997 (Box 2.013, Folder 2)
  - Animal Protection of New Mexico: AA3 - Correspondence, 1998 May 28 (Box 2.013, Folder 3)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.013, Folder 4)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA2 - Posters, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.013, Folder 5)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA3 - Solicitations, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.013, Folder 6)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA4 - Newsletters, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.013, Folder 7)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA5 - Bulletins, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.013, Folder 8)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA6 - Guide to animal rights, circa 1980 (Box 2.013, Folder 9)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA7 - Information kit, 1998 (Box 2.013, Folder 10)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA8 - Update relating to product testing, 1990s (Box 2.013, Folder 11)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA9 - Publications relating to companion animal food, 1997 (Box 2.013, Folder 12)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA10 - Report relating to cigarette smoke, 1997 (Box 2.013, Folder 13)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA11 - Reports relating to xenotransplantation, 1996 (Box 2.013, Folder 14)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA12 - Frontline Report, 1994 (Box 2.013, Folder 15)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA12 - Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 2.013, Folder 16)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA13 - Brochures, 1994-1997 (Box 2.013, Folder 17)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA14 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.014, Folder 1)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA15 - Leaflets, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.014, Folder 2)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA16 - Report relating to "Trapping on National Wildlife Refuges,", 1998 February (Box 2.014, Folder 3)
  - Animal Protection Institute (API): AA17 - Bulletins, 1996, 2000 (Box 2.014, Folder 4)
  - Animal Protection League (APL): AA1 - Bulletins, 1999 Spring/Summer (Box 2.014, Folder 5)
  - Animal Protection League -Hunter College (APL): AA1 - Newsletters, 1972-1973 (Box 2.014, Folder 6)
  - Animal Protection League of Okaloosa County, Ft. Walton Beach CA.(APL): AA1 - Correspondence, 1989 December 1 (Box 2.014, Folder 7)
  - Animal Protection Service (APS): AA1 - Correspondence, 1988 March 12 (Box 2.014, Folder 8)
  - Animal Rights Coalition (ARC): P1 - Newsletters, 1983-1987 (Box 2.014, Folder 9)
  - Animal Rights Connection (ARC): P1 - Newsletters, 1984-1987 (Box 2.014, Folder 10)
  - The Animal Rights Alliance (ARA): P1 - Newsletters, 1984- 1988 (Box 2.014, Folder 11)
  - The Animal Rights Alliance (ARA): P2 - Pamphlets, 1988 (Box 2.014, Folder 12)
  - Animal Protective Association of Missouri, St. Louis Missouri (APA): AA1 - Newsletters, 1995-2000 (Box 2.014, Folder 13)
  - Animal Protective Foundation of Schenectady, Inc. Scotia NY (APF): AA1 - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 2.014, Folder 14)
  - Animal Refuge Center Inc., Fort Meyers, Fla.(ARC): AA1 - Newsletter, 1993 September/October (Box 2.014, Folder 15)
  - Animal Refuge Center Inc., Vine Grove, KY (ARC): AA1 - Pamphlet, 1980s (Box 2.014, Folder 16)
  - Animal Refuge Center Inc., Vine Grove, KY (ARC): AA2 - Newsletters, 1992-1993 (Box 2.014, Folder 17)
  - Animal Refuge Center Inc., Vine Grove, KY (ARC): AA2 - Voices from the ARC, 1989, 1995-1999 (Box 2.014, Folder 18)
  - Animal Research Digest (ARD): AA1 - Newsletter, 1998 January (Box 2.014, Folder 19)
  - Animal Rights Information Service, Inc. N.Y.N.Y. (ARIS): AA1 - Pamphlets, 198-? (Box 2.014, Folder 20)
  - Animal Rights Information Service, Inc.N.Y.N.Y. (ARIS): AA2 - Bulletins, 1985 (Box 2.014, Folder 21)
  - Animal Rescue Force, Inc., Forest Hills N.Y. (ARF): AA1 - Newsletters, 1992 November (Box 2.014, Folder 22)
  - Animal Rescue Force, Inc., Forest Hills N.Y. (ARF): AA2 - News clippings, 1989, 1996 (Box 2.014, Folder 23)
  - Animal Rescue, Liverpool England (AR): AA1 - Newsletter, 1995 (Box 2.014, Folder 24)
  - Animal Rescue Foundation: AA1 - Bulletins, circa 1992 (Box 2.014, Folder 25)
  - Animal Rescue, Inc. Maryland Line, MD.: AA1 - Leaflets, 1995, 1998 (Box 2.014, Folder 26)
  - Animal Rescue, Inc. Maryland Line, MD.: AA2 - Newsletters, 1993-1994 (Box 2.014, Folder 27)
  - Animal Rescue Foundation (ARF): AA1 Grant proposal, 1997 (Box 2.014, Folder 28)
  - Animal Rescue League of Boston (ARL): AA1 - Magazine Our four footed friends, 1992 Spring (Box 2.014, Folder 29)
  - Animal Rescue Action League (ARAL): AA1 - Newsletters, 1991 (Box 2.014, Folder 30)
  - Animal Rights Advocates of the Hudson Valley (ARAHV): AA1 - Newsletters, 1989, 1991 (Box 2.014, Folder 31)
  - Animal Rights Advocates of Western New York: AA1 - Pamphlets, 1990s (Box 2.014, Folder 32)
  - Animal Rights Alliance (ARA): AA1 - Newsletters, 1988-1989 (Box 2.014, Folder 33)
  - Animal Rights Alliance (ARA): AA2 - News clippings, 1988 (Box 2.014, Folder 34)
  - Animal Rights Alliance of South Carolina: AA1 - Correspondence, 1992 March 28 (Box 2.014, Folder 35)
  - Animal Rights America, Inc.: AA1 - Press releases, 1996 (Box 2.014, Folder 36)
  - Animal Rights Association: AA1 - Catalogs, 1993 (Box 2.015, Folder 1)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, Arizona(ARC): AA1 - News clippings, 1987 (Box 2.015, Folder 2)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, Indiana (ARC): AA1 - News clippings, 1988 (Box 2.015, Folder 3)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, Maryland (ARC): AA1 - News clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 2.015, Folder 4)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, Minnesota (ARC): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1980s (Box 2.015, Folder 5)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, Minnesota (ARC): AA2 - Printed matter, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.015, Folder 6)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, Minnesota (ARC): AA3 - News clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.015, Folder 7)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, Penn. (ARC): AA1 - Newsletters, 1991 (Box 2.015, Folder 8)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, San Diego. (ARC): AA1 - Newsletters, 1984 (Box 2.015, Folder 9)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, Sanford Fla. (ARC): AA1 - Pamphlet, 1980s (Box 2.015, Folder 10)
  - Animal Rights Coalition, Sanford Fla. (ARC): AA2 - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2.015, Folder 11)
  - Animal Rights Committee (ARC): AA1 - Newsletter, 1991 (Box 2.015, Folder 12)
  - Animal Rights Connection (ARC): AA1 - Printed matter, 1986 (Box 2.015, Folder 13)
  - Animal Rights Connection (ARC): AA2 - News clipping, 1989 March 8 (Box 2.015, Folder 14)
  - Animal Rights Council (ARC): AA1- Bulletins, 1989-1990 (Box 2.015, Folder 15)
  - Animal Rights Foundation Florida (ARFF): AA1- Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.015, Folder 16)
  - Animal Rights Foundation Florida (ARFF): AA2 - News clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.015, Folder 17)
  - Animal Rights Foundation Florida (ARFF): AA3 - Correspondence, 1990s (Box 2.015, Folder 18)
  - Animal Rights International N.Y.N.Y. (ARI): AA1 - Advertisements, 1991 (Box 2.015, Folder 19)
  - Animal Rights International N.Y.N.Y. (ARI): AA2 -Newsletter, 1995 (Box 2.015, Folder 20)
  - Animal Rights International N.Y.N.Y. (ARI): AA3 - Statistical report, 1998 March 13 (Box 2.015, Folder 21)
  - Animal Rights Front (ARF): AA1 - Leaflets, 1980s (Box 2.015, Folder 22)
  - Animal Rights Front (ARF): AA2 - Newsletters, 1982-1983, 1993 April (Box 2.015, Folder 23)
  - Animal Rights Front (ARF): AA3 - News clippings, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 2.015, Folder 24)
  - Animal Rights Hawaii (ARH): AA1 - Newsletters, 1996 (Box 2.015, Folder 25)
  - Animal Rights Hawaii (ARH): AA2 - Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 2.015, Folder 26)
  - Animal Rights Hawaii (ARH): AA3 - Published articles, 1995 January (Box 2.015, Folder 27)
  - Animal Rights Hawaii (ARH): AA4 - News clipping, 1995 January 11 (Box 2.015, Folder 28)
  - Animal Rights Hawaii (ARH): AA5 - Information kit, 1987, 1991-1996 (Box 2.015, Folder 29)
  - Animal Rights Network (ARN): AA1 - Printed matter, 1988 (Box 2.015, Folder 30)
  - Animal Rights Network (ARN): AA2 - Correspondence, 1982 July 7 (Box 2.015, Folder 31)
  - Animal Rights Network (ARN): AA3 - Published articles, 1983 May (Box 2.015, Folder 32)
  - Animal Rights Network (ARN): AA4 - News clipping, 1988 July 12 (Box 2.015, Folder 33)
  - Animal Rights Network (ARN): AA5 - Proposals, 1980 May 6 (Box 2.015, Folder 34)
  - The Animal Shelter and Wildlife Society, Winter Garden FL: AA1 - Newsletters, 1990s (Box 2.015, Folder 35)
  - The Animal Shelter and Wildlife Society, Winter Garden FL: AA2 - Pamphlets, 1990s (Box 2.015, Folder 36)
  - Animal S.O.S., Czechoslovakia: AA1 - Magazine, 1991 (Box 2.015, Folder 37)
  - Animal Voice of South Africa: AA1 - newsletter, 1994 Winter (Box 2.015, Folder 38)
  - Animal Watch (AWA): AA1 - Bulletins, 1997 March 30, 1997 November 11 (Box 2.015, Folder 39)
  - Animal Watch (AWA): AA2 - Published articles(Press release), 1997 June 15 (Box 2.015, Folder 40)
  - Animal Watch Sacramento CA: AA1 - Correspondence, 1995 February 3 (Box 2.015, Folder 41)
  - Animal Watch Sacramento CA: AA2 - Newsletters, 1995 January, April (Box 2.015, Folder 42)
  - Animal Welfare Alliance (AWA): AA1 - Newsletters, 1991, 1994-1996 (Box 2.015, Folder 43)
  - Animal Welfare Alliance (AWA): AA2 - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 2.015, Folder 44)
  - Animal Welfare Alliance (AWA): AA3 - Bulletins, 1994-1995 (Box 2.015, Folder 45)
  - Animal Welfare Council: AA1 - Newsletters, 1998 Spring (Box 2.016, Folder 1)
  - Animal Welfare Council: AA2 - Report, 1998 (Box 2.016, Folder 2)
  - Animal Welfare Council: AA3 - List of board of directors, 1998 (Box 2.016, Folder 3)
  - Animal Rights Mobilization (ARM): AA1 - Legislation, 1998 (Box 2.016, Folder 4)
  - Animal Rights Mobilization (ARM): AA2 - Information kits, 1993 (Box 2.016, Folder 5)
  - Animal Rights Mobilization (ARM): AA3 - Newsletters, 1992-1998 (Box 2.016, Folder 6)
  - Animal Rights Mobilization (ARM): AA4 - Bulletins, 1992-1995 (Box 2.016, Folder 7)
  - Animal Rights Mobilization (ARM): AA5 - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 2.016, Folder 8)
  - Animal Rights Mobilization (ARM): AA6 - News clippings, 1992 (Box 2.016, Folder 9)
  - Animal Welfare Institute (AWI): AA1 - Printed matter, 1990s (Box 2.016, Folder 10)
  - Animal Welfare Institute (AWI): AA2 - Guide to publications and films, 1990s (Box 2.016, Folder 11)
  - Animal Welfare Institute (AWI): AA3 - Published articles, 1993 Summer (Box 2.016, Folder 12)
  - Animal Welfare Institute (AWI): AA4 - Annual reports, 1991-1992, 1992-1993, 1994-1995 (Box 2.016, Folder 13)
  - The Animal Welfare Association (AWA): AA1 - Report, 1984 (Box 2.016, Folder 14)
  - Animal Welfare Foundation: AA1 - News clipping, 1990 August 9 (Box 2.016, Folder 15)
  - Animal Welfare, Inc.: AA1 - Newsletter, 1988 Spring (Box 2.016, Folder 16)
  - Animal Welfare League, Chicago Ridge IL.: AA! - Newsletters, 1999-2000 (Box 2.016, Folder 17)
  - Animal Welfare League of Arlington: AA! - Magazines(Newsletters), 1996-1997 (Box 2.016, Folder 18)
  - Animal Welfare League of Baltimore: AA! - Newsletter, 1995 (Box 2.016, Folder 19)
  - Animal Welfare League of Charlotte County, Fla.: AA! - Bulletin for "Kitty College,", 1995-1996 (Box 2.016, Folder 20)
  - Animal Welfare League of New London County, Inc..: AA! - Newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box 2.016, Folder 21)
  - Animal Welfare League of Westchester County, Inc..: AA! - Newsletter, 1989 August (Box 2.016, Folder 22)
  - Animal Welfare and Responsibility Effort (AWARE): AA! - News clipping, 1992 March 27 (Box 2.016, Folder 23)
  - AnimaLiberation, Orlando Fla.: AA1 - Press releases, 1990 August 30, 1990 November 9 (Box 2.016, Folder 24)
  - Animaline and Orphanage: AA1 - Bulletin, circa 1990 (Box 2.016, Folder 25)
  - Animanity: AA1 - Newspaper, 1996 January (Box 2.016, Folder 26)
  - Animals and the Environment: AA1 - Bulletin, 1994 (Box 2.017, Folder 2)
  - Animals Can't talk, Whitestone, NY: AA1 - Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 2.017, Folder 3)
  - The Animals' Crusaders, Everett Washington: AA1 - Printed matter, 1980s (Box 2.017, Folder 4)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA1 - Organizational materials, 1952-1992 (Box 2.017, Folder 5)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA2 - Organizational materials, 1974-1996 (Box 2.017, Folder 6)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA3 - News clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 2.017, Folder 7)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA4 - Legal materials accompanied by correspondence, newsletter, News clippings, 1990s (Box 2.017, Folder 8)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA5 - Legal materials accompanied by correspondence, newsletter, News clippings, 1955-1980s (Box 2.017, Folder 9)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA6 - Printed matter from other animal rights organizations, News clippings, 1990s (Box 2.017, Folder 10)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA8 - Materials on attempt to organize federation, 1983-1986 (Box 2.018, Folder 1)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA9 - Newsletters, 1987-1988 (Box 2.018, Folder 2)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA10 - Correspondence, 1958-1994 (Box 2.018, Folder 3)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA11 - News clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.018, Folder 4)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA12 - Pamphlets, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.018, Folder 5)
  - Animals' Crusaders of Arizona: AA13 - Miscellaneous materials: photographs, pamphlets, bulletins, correspondence, newsletters and News clippings, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.018, Folder 6)
  - Animals Deserve Adequate Protection today and Tomorrow (ADAPTT): AA1 - Newsletters, 1998-1999 (Box 2.018, Folder 7)
  - Animals Disaster team in Cuyahoga County, Cleveland Ohio (ADT): AA1 - Pamphlet, 1994 (Box 2.018, Folder 8)
  - Animals Have Hearts Too!, Waco Texas (AHHT): AA1 - Correspondence, 1994 September 22 (Box 2.018, Folder 9)
  - Animals Have Hearts Too!, Waco Texas (AHHT): AA2 - News clippings, 1994 (Box 2.018, Folder 10)
  - Animals Have Hearts Too!, Warren Mich. (AHHT): AA1 -Correspondence, 1994 August 1 (Box 2.018, Folder 11)
  - Animals In Distress, Wilton Conn.. (AID): AA1 - Newsletters, 1987, 1993-1999 (Box 2.018, Folder 12)
  - Animals In Politics N.Y.N.Y. (AIP): AA1 - Report, 1986 April (Box 2.018, Folder 13)
  - Animals Protected in Entertainment (APE): AA1 - Published article, 1994 May 17 (Box 2.018, Folder 14)
  - The Animals' Voice, Canoga Park, Ca.: AA1 - Newsletters, 1987 (Box 2.018, Folder 15)
  - The Animals' Voice, Canoga Park, Ca.: AA2 - News clippings, 198-? (Box 2.018, Folder 16)
  - Animated Dissection of Anatomy for Medicine (ADAM): AA1 - Media kit, 1995 (Box 2.018, Folder 17)
  - AnimEarth Project, Fukuoka, Japan: AA1 - Leaflet, 1997 (Box 2.018, Folder 18)
  - ANIPAC, Pittsburgh Pa.: AA1 - Newsletters, 1988, 1990 (Box 2.018, Folder 19)
  - Anonymous for Animal Rights: AA1 - Bulletin, 1999 (Box 2.018, Folder 20)
  - Another Place, Mettanokit Outreach, New Hampshire: AA1 - Newsletter, 1992 Summer (Box 2.018, Folder 21)
  - Aanati-Bullfighting Campaign International, Barcelona Spain: AA1 - Newsletters, 1995-1998 (Box 2.018, Folder 22)
  - Anti-Cruelty Association, Detroit Michigan: AA1 - Newsletter, 1991 Fall (Box 2.018, Folder 23)
  - Anti-Dairy Coalition (ADC): AA1 - published article, 1998 June 15 (Box 2.018, Folder 24)
  - Antrim County Pet and Animal Watch, Mancelona, Michigan (A.C. PAW): AA1 - Correspondence, 1997 February 24 (Box 2.019, Folder 1)
  - Aperture: AA1 - Catalog, 1999 Spring (Box 2.019, Folder 2)
  - Arizona People for Animals Rights, Gilbert Az. (APAR): AA1 - Printed matter, 1995 (Box 2.019, Folder 3)
  - Arizona People for Animals Rights, Gilbert Az. (APAR): AA2 - Invitations, 1994-1995 (Box 2.019, Folder 4)
  - Arizona People for Animals Rights, Gilbert Az. (APAR): AA3 - Newsletters, 1994-1995 (Box 2.019, Folder 5)
  - ARC Update, Midlothian, TX. (ARC): AA1 - Newsletters, 1991 (Box 2.019, Folder 6)
  - Artenschutz-Info, Korntal-Munchingen, Germany: AA1 - Newsletters, 1991, 1993 (Box 2.019, Folder 7)
  - The Ark Trust, Inc., Encino, Ca.: AA1 - Printed Matter, 1980s-1990s (Box 2.019, Folder 8)
  - The Ark Trust, Inc., Encino, Ca.: AA2 - Programs, 1995, 1997 (Box 2.019, Folder 9)
  - The Ark Trust, Inc., Encino, Ca.: AA3- Programs, 1993, 1998, 1999 (Box 2.019, Folder 10)
  - The Ark Trust, Inc., Encino, Ca.: AA4- Information kits, 1993 (Box 2.019, Folder 11)
  - The Ark Trust, Inc., Encino, Ca.: AA5- Correspondence, 1996 July 11, 1997 September 18 (Box 2.019, Folder 12)
  - The Ark Trust, Inc., Encino, Ca.: AA6 - Programs, 1996, 2000 (Box 2.02, Folder 1)
  - AEK II, the Animal Rights Kollective, Toronto, Ontario Canada: AA1 - Newsletters, 1990s (Box 2.02, Folder 2)
  - AEK II, the Animal Rights Kollective, Toronto, Ontario Canada: AA2 - Printed matter, 1996, 1998 (Box 2.02, Folder 3)
  - AEK II, the Animal Rights Kollective, Toronto, Ontario Canada: AA3 - Report, 1993 January (Box 2.02, Folder 4)
  - Arkansas For Animals, Inc., Little Rock Arkansas (AFA): AA1 - Newsletter, 1998 Spring (Box 2.02, Folder 5)
  - ARRS: AA1 - Articles, 1992-1995 (Box 2.02, Folder 6)
  - Asia-Pacific People's Environment Network (APPEN): AA1 - Bulletins, 1988 (Box 2.02, Folder 7)
  - Asians For Humans, Animals and Nature (AHAN): AA1 - Press release, 1998 October 7 (Box 2.02, Folder 8)
  - Aspen Society for Animal Rights (ASFAR): AA1 - Bulletin, 1990 February 3 (Box 2.02, Folder 9)
  - Aspen Society for Animal Rights (ASFAR): AA2 - News clipping, 1990 February 2 (Box 2.02, Folder 10)
  - Assisi International Animal Institute(AIAI): AA1- Information kit, 1998 July 3 (Box 2.02, Folder 11)
  - Associacioacute; Protectora D'Animals I Plantes Tossa De Mar: AA1 - Bulletins, 1990-1991 (Box 2.02, Folder 12)
  - Associacioacute; Protectora D'Animals I Plantes Tossa De Mar: AA2 - News clipping, 1989 December 10 (Box 2.02, Folder 13)
  - Asociación Amigos de los Animales, Panama, Republic of Panama: AA1 - Solicitation, 1993 September 10 (Box 2.02, Folder 14)
  - Asociacioacute;n Defensora de los animales: AA1 - Bulletin, 1998 August 1 (Box 2.02, Folder 15)
  - Asociacioacute;n Latinoamericana en Defensa de los Animales N.Y.N.Y. (ALDA): AA1 - Pamphlets, 1990s (Box 2.02, Folder 16)
  - Asociacioacute;n Latinoamericana en Defensa de los Animales N.Y.N.Y. (ALDA): AA2 - Bulletin, 1990 (Box 2.02, Folder 17)